A Guide to the Williams C. Wooldridge papers, ca. 1960-2015
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Williams C. Wooldridge papers, ca. 1960-2015
The Library of Virginia
51624
12.25 cu. ft. and 27 boxes
William C. Wooldridge
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of William C. Wooldridge of Suffolk, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1960-2015, of William C. Wooldridge of Suffolk, Virginia, consisting of articles, Bible records, brochures, census records, correspondence, court records, death records, deeds, genealogical notes, interviews, marriage records, military records, obituaries, pamphlets, photographs, wills, and other papers compiled by Laurence B. Gardiner (1906-1994) and Wooldridge chronicling the genealogy of the descendants of John Wooldridge (ca. 1678-1757) of Henrico and Chesterfield Counties, Virginia. Collection includes books written by various members of the Wooldridge family on various topics and ephemera relating to members of the Wooldridge family and their business interests.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: John[2] (ca. 1705-1783]
Series II: Thomas[2] (ca. 1707-1762)
Series III: William[2] (ca. 1709-1798)
Series IV: Edward[2] (ca. 1711-1808)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Other Finding Aid
Consult both the on-line finding aid and the hard copy finding aid located in the first folder in the first box of the collection.
Contents List
- Introduction. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1. John Wooldridge (ca. 1678-1757). (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series I: John[2] (ca. 1705-1783) son of 1.John., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 1-6)
  John[2] contains papers on the descendants of John Wooldridge (ca. 1705-1783), son of John Wooldridge (ca. 1678-1757).
  - 2. John Wooldridge[2] (ca. 1705-1783) son of 1.John. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 8. Richard[3] son of 2.John. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 57. John[4] son of 8.Richard. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 239. Thomas[5] son of 57.John. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 240. Judith[5] daughter of 57.John. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 241. George[5] son of 57.John. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 242. John C.[5] son of 57.John. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 243. William C.[5] son of 57.John. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 244. Edmund B.[5] son of 57.John. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 58. Elizabeth[4] daughter of 8.Richard (empty folder). (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 247. ?Lucy[5] daughter of 58.Elizabeth; 248. ?Frances[5] daughter of 58.Elizabeth; 249. ?Elizabeth[5] daughter of 58.Elizabeth. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 250. ?Mary[5] daughter of 58.Elizabeth. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 59. Richard[4] son of 8.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 252. ?Daniel[5] son of 59.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 253. Virlinchege[5] daughter of 59.Richard); 255. ?Elizabeth[5] daughter of 59.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 254. ?William S.[5] son of 59.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 256. ?Richard D.[5] son of 59.Richard (folder 1 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 256. ?Richard D.[5] son of 59.Richard (folder 2 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 257. ?John[5] son of 59.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 258. Mary[5] daughter of 59.Richard; 259. Hannah[5] daughter of 59.Richard; 260. ?Rhoda[5] daughter of 59.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 60. Mary[4] daughter of 8.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 61. William[4] son of 8.Richard. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 263. Dabney Ellis[5] son of 61.William. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 264. Harker Hutcheson[5] daughter of 61.William; 265. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 61.William; 266. Phoebe Jane[5] daughter of 61.William; 267. Nancy Elizabeth[5] daughter of 61.William. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 62. Jenny[4] daughter of 8.Richard; 63. Phoebe[4] daughter of 8.Richard; 64.Sarah[4] daughter of 8.Richard (empty folder). (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 9. John[3] son of 2.John. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 65. Elizabeth Branch[4] daughter of 9.John. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 66. James[4] son of 9.John. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 272. Mary[5] daughter of 66.James; 273. ?Nancy[5] daughter of 66.James. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 274. John J.[5] son of 66.James (folder 1 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 274. John J.[5] son of 66.James (folder 2 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 275. Rebecca[5] daughter of 66.James. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 276. Samuel C.[5] son of 66.James (folder 1 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 276. Samuel C.[5] son of 66.James (folder 2 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 277. Keziah[5] daughter of 66.James. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 278. Peter Staples[5] son of 66.James (folder 1 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 278. Peter Staples[5] son of 66.James (folder 2 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 278. Peter Staples[5] son of 66.James (folder 3 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - C. E. Wooldridge (b. 1912) son of William Edward, son of A.Louis A. son of ii.James, son of 278.Peter. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Laura A. Wooldridge, sister or half-sister of Lewis Aldophus Wooldridge (from 258.Mary and 278.Peter S.). (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 279. Lewellen J.[5] son of 66.James. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 67. ?Sarah[4] daughter of 9.John; 69. -----[4] daughter of 9.John (possibly md. Franklin) (empty folder). (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 68. John[4] son of 9.John (empty folder). (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 282. Mary[5] daughter of 68.John; 284. Thomas[5] son of 68.John; 285. John[5] son of 68.John; 286 Elizabeth[5] daughter of 68.John. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 283. Loving[5] son of 68.John. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 10. Mary[3] daughter of 2.John. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 11. William[3] son of 2.John. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 70. Fleming[4] son of 11.William; 71. Harrison[4] son of 11.William. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 72. Edmund[4] son of 11.William. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 290. Thomas[5] son of 72.Edmund. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 291. William[5] son of 72.Edmund. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 292. Daniel[5] son of 72.Edmund. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 73. William Harrison[4] son of 11.William. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 297. Elam Sparks[5] son of 73.William Harrison; 298. Nancy Emaline[5] daughter of 73.William Harrison. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 74. Mary[4] daughter of 11.William; 75. ?Elizabeth[4] daughter of 11.William. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 12. Elizabeth[3] daughter of 2.John. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 13. Frances?[3] daughter of 2.John (empty folder). (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 14. Edmund[3] son of 2.John. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 76. Edmund[4] son of 14.Edmund. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 77. Samuel C.[4] son of 14.Edmund. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 300. Ann Eliza[5] daughter of 77.Samuel C.; 301. Henry Clay[5] son of 77.Samuel C.; 304. Narcissa Texas[5] daughter of 77.Samuel C.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 302. Samuel Dunbar[5] son of 77.Samuel C. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 303. Edmund Collins[5] son of 77.Samuel C. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 78.Phoebe[4] daughter of 14.Edmund; 79. Nancy[4] daughter of 14.Edmund. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 80. John Watkins[4] son of 14.Edmund. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 305. John Watkins[5] son of 80.John Watkins; 306. Emily C.[5] daughter of John Watkins; 307. Powhatan[5] son of John Watkins; 308. Mary Ann Elizabeth[5] daughter of 80.John Watkins; 310. Jane Elizabeth[5] daughter of 80.John Watkins. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 309. Lucian Powhatan[5] son of 80.John Watkins. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 81. Powhatan[4] son of 14.Edmund. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 311. Cora Virginia[5] daughter of 81.Powhatan; 313. Isabel Taylor[5] daughter of 81.Powhatan. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 312. Edmund[5] son of 81.Powhatan. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 314. John Major[5] son of 81.Powhatan. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 315. Samuel Louis[5] son of 81.Powhatan. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 316. William Henry[5] son of 81.Powhatan; 318. Mildred Elvira[5] daughter of 81.Powhatan (empty folder). (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 317. Powhatan[5] son of 81.Powhatan. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 15. Virlinche[3] daughter of 2.John; 16. Phebe[3] daughter of 2.John. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 17. Robert[3] son of 2.John. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 82. Merritt S.[4] son of 17.Robert; 83. John[4] son of 17.Robert; 84 Elizabeth Redd[4] daughter of 17.Robert (empty folder). (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 85. Thomas Major[4] son of 17.Robert. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 320. Lucian[5] son of 85.Thomas Major; 323. Annie[5] daughter of 85.Thomas Major; 324. Katherine[5] daughter of 85.Thomas Major. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 321. Joseph Cates[5] son of 85.Thomas Major. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 322. Robert Madison[5] son of 85.Thomas Major. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 18. Thomas[3] son of 2.John. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 86. John Barnes[4] son of 18.Thomas; 87. Mary P.[4] daughter of 18.Thomas; 88. Elizabeth[4] daughter of 18.Thomas. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 89. Edmund Porter[4] son of 18.Thomas; 90. ?George[4] son of 18.Thomas. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 330. Mary[5] daughter of 89.Edmund Porter; 331. Thomas[5] son of 89.Edmund Porter; 332. Lillie Ellen[5] daughter of 89.Edmund Porter. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 333. Robert Atchison[5] son of 89.Edmund Porter. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 334. Harriet B.[5] daughter of 89.Edmund Porter; 335. Sarah Ann Barnes[5] daughter of 89.Edmund Porter; 336. George[5] son of 89.Edmund Porter; 337. John[5] son of 89.Edmund Porter. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 19. Martha[3] daughter of 2.John. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 20. Hanna[3] daughter of 2.John. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Series II: Thomas[2] (ca. 1707-1762) son of 1.John., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 6-7)
  Thomas[2] contains papers on the descendants of Thomas Wooldridge (ca. 1707-1762), son of John Wooldridge (ca. 1678-1757).
  - 3. Thomas Wooldridge[2] (ca. 1707-1762) son of 1.John. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 21. John[3] son of 3.Thomas. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 91. Thomas[4] son of 21.John. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 345. John[5] son of 91.Thomas. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 346. ?Sally[5] daughter of 91.Thomas; 347. Mary[5] daughter of 91.Thomas. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 348. Joseph[5] son of 91.Thomas. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 92. Seth[4] son of 21.John. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 352. Daniel[5] son of 92.Seth; 353. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 92.Seth (empty folder). (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 354. Elam[5] son of 92.Seth. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 355. Virlinchia[5] daughter of 92.Seth; 356. Seth[5] son of 92.Seth; 358. Chastain[5] son of 92.Seth; 359. Phoebe[5] daughter of 92.Seth (empty folder). (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 357. John[5] son of 92.Seth. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 360. Washington[5] son of 92.Seth. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 361. William Thomas[5] son of 92.Seth. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 93. Frances[4] daughter of 21.John; 94.Phoebe[4] daughter of 21.John (empty folder). (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 95. John[4] son of 21.John. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 363. Matilda[5] daughter of 95.John; 364. Caroline[5] daughter of 95.John; 365. Wade W.[5] son of 95.John. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 96. ?Daniel[4] son of 21.John. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 367. Edward[5] son of 96.Daniel. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 368. Gilbert[5] son of 96.Daniel. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 369. Phebe Ann Frances[5] daughter of 96.Daniel; 370. Lucy Jane[5] daughter of 96.Daniel; 371. Susan[5] daughter of 96.Daniel (empty folder). (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 372. Archer Daniel[5] son of 96.Daniel. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 22. Frances[3] daughter of 3.Thomas; 23. Mary[3] daughter of 3.Thomas; 24. Elizabeth[3] daughter of 3.Thomas. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 25. Thomas[3] son of 3.Thomas (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 97. ?Thomas, Jr.[5] son of 25.Thomas (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 375. ?Nancy[5] daugther of 97.Thomas, Jr.; 377. ?Thomas[5] son of 97.Thomas, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 376. ?George H.[5] son of 97.Thomas, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 98. Charles[4] son of 25.Thomas; 99. Polly[4] daughter of 25.Thomas; 100. George[4] son of 25.Thomas; 101 ?John S.[4] son of 25.Thomas; 102. Elizabeth Hooper[4] daughter of 25.Thomas; 103. -----[4] daughter of 25.Thomas. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 26. Henry[3] son of 3.Thomas. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 104. John (F.?)[4] son of 26.Henry; 105. ?Daniel[4] son of 26.Henry. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 385. ?Elizabeth[5] daughter of 105.Daniel; 386. ?Mary J.[5] daughter of 105.Daniel (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 27. Martha[3] daughter of 3.Thomas (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 28. Daniel[3] son of 3.Thomas. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 110. Elizabeth[4] daughter of 28.Daniel; 112. Sarah Pigg[4] daughter of 28.Daniel; 113. Frances H.[4] daughter of 28.Daniel; 114. Nance Jones[4] daughter of 28.Daniel; 115. Caroline[4] daughter of 28.Daniel. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 111. Spencer[4] son of 28.Daniel. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 390. John[5] son of 111.Spencer. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 391. Daniel Spencer[5] son of 111.Spencer. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 392. Joseph R.[5] son of 111.Spencer (folder 1 of 2). (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 392. Joseph R.[5] son of 111.Spencer (folder 2 of 2). (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 393. Mary Hannah[5] daughter of 111.Spencer; 394. Martha F.[5] daughter of 111.Spencer; 395. Richard T.[5] Son of 111.Spencer; Rebecca S.[5] daughter of 111.Spencer. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 29. Joseph[3] son of 3.Thomas. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 116. Joe (Joseph Andersdon)[4] son of 29.Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 117. Francis Marion[4] son of 29.Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 400. Mary Ann Frances[5] daughter of 117.Francis Marion; 401. Martha Jane[5] daughter of 117.Francis Marion; 402. Amanda Booker[5] daughter of 117.Francis Marion. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 403. John Braxton Henry[5] son of 117.Francis Marion. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 404. Robert Nicholas[5] son of 117.Francis Marion. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 405. Francis Monroe[5] son of 117.Francis Marion. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 406. William Daniel[5] son of 117.Francis Marion. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 407. Harriet Cole[5] daughter of 117.Francis Marion (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 118. Edmund[4] son of 29.Joseph (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 410. Adeline[5] daughter of 118.Edmund; 411. Mary S.[5] daughter of 118.Edmund (empty folder0. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 412. Edward Clifford[5] son of 118.Edmund. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 119. William B.[4] son of 29.Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 415. Martha[5] daughter of 119.William B.; 416. Lettia[5] daughter of 119.William B.; 417. Narcissa[5] daughter of 119.William B. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 418. William H.[5] son of 119.William B. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 419. Caroline[5] daughter of 119.William B.; 420. John[5] son of 119.William B.; 421. Harriet[5] daughter of 119.William B.; 422. Edward B.[5] son of 119.William B.; 423. Missouri Eliza[5] daughter of 119.William B.; 424. Ellen[5] daughter of 119.William B.; 425. Louisa[5] daughter of 119.William B. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 120. ?Elizabeth W.[4] daughter of 29.Joseph; 120.1. Susan[4] daughter of 29.Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 121. Harrison[4] son of 29.Joseph (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 427. Sarah Anne Elizabeth[5] daughter of 121. Harrison; 428. Henry William[5] son of 121.Harrison (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 122. Thomas Powhatan[4] son of 29.Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 430. Emma L. or Ermina[5] daughter of 122.Thomas Powhatan; 431. Edwin Augustine[5] son of 122.Thomas Powhatan; 432. Charles Augustus[5] son of 122.Thomas Powhatan; 433. Sarah Maria[5] Mattie daughter of 122.Thomas Powhatan; 434. Elizabeth[5] Lizzie daughter of 122.Thomas Powhatan (empty folder). (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 123. John Henry[4] son of 29.Joseph; 124. Celia[4] daughter of 29.Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Series III: William[2] (ca. 1709-1798) son of 1.John., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 8-14)
  William[2] contains papers on the descendants of William Wooldridge (ca. 1709-1798), son of John Wooldridge (ca. 1678-1757).
  - 4. William Wooldridge[2] (ca. 1709-1798) son of 1.John. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 30. Richard[3] son of 4.William (folder 1 of 3). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 30. Richard[3] son of 4.William (folder 2 of 3). (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 30. Richard[3] son of 4.William (folder 3 of 3). (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 125. James[4] son of 30.Richard. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 435. Fannie[5] daughter of 125.James; 436. Elizabeth[5] Betsy daughter of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 437. Jesse[5] son of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 438. James, Jr.[5] son of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 439. Stephen[5] son of 125.James; 440. Sallie W.[5] daughter of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 441. Lewis W.[5] son of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 442. Nancy[5] daughter of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 443. Jane[5] daughter of 125.James; 444. Lucinda[5] daughter of 125.James; Martha[5] Patsy daughter of 125.James. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 126. Fanny[4] daughter of 30.Richard (folder 1 of 2). (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 126. Fanny[4] daughter of 30.Richard. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 127. John[4] son of 30.Richard. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 448. Jane[5] daughter of 127.John (empty folder). (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 449. Samuel[5] son of 127.John (folder 1 of 3). (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 449. Samuel[5] son of 127.John (folder 2 of 3). (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 449. Samuel[5] son of 127.John (folder 3 of 3). (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 450. William[5] son of 127.John. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 451. ?Elliott[5] son of 127.John; 452. Elzabeth[5] daughter of 127.John; 453. Gallatin[5] son of 127.John (folder 1 of 2). (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 451. ?Elliott[5] son of 127.John; 452. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 127.John; 453. Gallatin[5] son of 127.John (folder 2 of 2). (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 454. John B.[5] son of 127.John. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 128. Elizabeth[4] daughter of 30.Richard. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 129. William[4] son of 30.Richard. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 458. Robert[5] son of 129.William (folder 1 of 2). (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 458. Robert[5] son of 129.William (folder 2 of 2). (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 459. Richard[5] son of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 460. Sara[5] daughter of 129.William; 461. Jane[5] daughter of 129.William; 462. Mary[5] daughter of 129.William; 468. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 463. William, Jr.[5] son of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 464. Edmond[5] son of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 465. Lott[5] son of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 466. Larkin[5] son of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 467. Dillingham[5] son of 129.William. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 130. Richard[4] son of 30.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 470. David[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 471. James[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 472. Thomas[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 473. William[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 474. Rutha[5] daughter of 130.Richard; 475. Mahala E.[5] daughter of 130.Richard; 476. Happy Arabella[5] daughter of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 477. Samuel M.[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 478. Reuben[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 479. Robert C.[5] son of 130.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 131. Mary[4] Polly daughter of 30.Richard. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 132. Sally[4] daughter of 30.Richard. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 482. Alexander[5] son of 132.Sally (folder 1 of 3). (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 482. Alexander[5] son of 132.Sally (folder 2 of 3). (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 482. Alexander[5] son of 132.Sally (folder 3 of 3). (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 133. Patsy[4] daughter of 30.Richard (empty folder). (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 134. Jesse[4] son of 30.Richard. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 484. John[5] son of 134.Jesse; 485. Christian[5] son of 134.Jesse. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 486. Abner[5] son of 134.Jesse. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 487. Martin[5] son of 134.Jesse. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 488. Edward[5] son of 134.Jesse (folder 1 of 2). (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 488. Edward[5] son of 134.Jesse (folder 2 of 2). (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 489. Elizabeth Jane[5] daughter of 134.Jesse. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 135. Jane[4] daughter of 30.Richard. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 31. William[3] son of 4.William. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 136. ?Samuel[5] son of 31.William. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 495. David[5] son of 136.Samuel (empty folder). (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 496. Mary[5] daughter of 136.Samuel; 497. Nancy[5] daughter of 136.Samuel; 498. Charlotte B.[5] daughter of 136.Samuel. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 499. Edmund[5] son of 136.Samuel. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 500. Starling R.[5] son of 136.Samuel. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 501. Margaret[5] daughter of 136.Samuel; 502. Susanna[5] daughter of 136.Samuel. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 503. Samuel, Jr.[5] son of 136.Samuel. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 137. Mary[4] daughter of 31.William (empty folder). (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 138. Thomas[4] spm of 31.William. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 505. Patsy[5] daughter of 138.Thomas; 507. Eliza Jane[5] daughter of 138.Thomas. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 506. John B.[5] son of 138.Thomas. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 508. Hugh B(radley?)[5] son of 138.Thomas. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 509. James B.[5] son of 138.Thomas. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 139. Sarah[4] daughter of 31.William; 140. ?Martha[4] daughter of 31.William; 141. Fanny[4] daughter of 31.William; 142. ?Phoebe[4] daughter of 31.William (empty folder). (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 143. ?Edmund[4] son of 31.William. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 513. Samuel[5] son of 143.Edmund; 514. Lucretia[5] daughter of 143.Edmund; 515. ----- Adams[5] daughter of 143.Edmund; 516. ----- Guthrie[5] daughter of 143.Edmund; 517. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 143.Edmund (empty folder). (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 32. Gibson[3] son of 4.William. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 144. John[4] son of 32.Gibson. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 520. Frances[5] daughter of 144.John. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 521. William H.[5] son of 144.John. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 522. Elizabeth[5] daughter of 144.John; 524. Lucy[5] daughter of 144.John; 526. Sarah P.[5] daughter of 144.John; 528. Harriet[5] daughter of 144.John; 523. Matilda[5] daughter of 144.John; 525. Nancy[5] daughter of 144.John. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 145. Robert[4] son of 32.Gibson. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 530. Isma W.[5] son of 145.Robert; 531. Gibson C.[5] son of 145.Robert. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 532. Absalom Davis[5] son of 145.Robert (folder 1 of 2). (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 532. Absalom Davis[5] son of 145.Robert (folder 2 of 2). (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 533. Thomas H.[5] son of 145.Robert; 534. ?Minerva[5] daughter of 145.Robert. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 146. Mary Ann[4] daughter of 32.Gibson. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 147. ?William[4] son of 32.Gibson. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 537. James Arnold[5] son of 147.William; 538. Barnett G.[5] son of 147. William. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 539. Caroline Jane[5] daughter of 147.William; 540. Samantha[5] daughter of 147.William. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 541. William M.[5] son of 147.William. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 542. John Gibson[5] son of 147.William. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 148. Elizabeth[4] daughter of 32.Gibson; 149. Sara Flournoy[5] daughter of 32.Gibson. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 150. Lucy or Martha[4] daughter of 32.Gibson. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 151. Thomas[4] son of 32.Gibson. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 545. Ludvicka[5] daughter of 151.Thomas; 546. ?Mary Barnes[5] daughter of 151.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 547. John R.[5] son of 151.Thomas; 548. Thomas[5] son of 151.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 549. Charlie A.[5] son of 151.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 33. Thomas[3] son of 4.William. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 152. Absalom Davis[5] son of 33.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 552. Martha Ann[5] daughter of 152.Absalom Davis; 553. Mary Henderson[5] daughter of 152.Absalom Davis; 556. Emily[5] daughter of 152.Absalom Davis; 557. Lucinda Caroline[5] daughter of 152.Absalom Davis (empty folder). (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 554. Thomas Flournoy[5] son of 152.Absalom Davis. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 555. William Gibson[5] son of 152.Absalom Davis. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 153. Martha[4] daughter of 33.Thomas; 154. William[4] son of 33.Thomas; 155. Sarah[4] daughter of 33.Thomas; 156. Penina[4] daughter of 33.Thomas; 157. Cinthy[4] daughter of 33.Thomas; 158. Pamelia[4] daughter of 33.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 159. Thomas D.[4] son of 33.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 160. Augustus B.[4] son of 33.Thomas. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 560. Thomas A.[4] son of 160.Ausgustus B. (Box 13, Folder 20)